http://www.aquaticcommunity.com/privacypolicy.htm

Privacy Police for ads
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google,
as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on
this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve
adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as
well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to
track users activities on this website to measure advertisement
effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own
privacy policies, this site has no access or control
over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
AquaticCommunity uses Viglink.com to monetize links to retailers and websites. Learn more about the technology by visiting viglink.com
AquaticCommunity
Privacy Policy
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That
is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know
how your personal information is processed and used. We garante that we will
take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible
with this Privacy Policy. The following discloses our Privacy Policy.
Information gathering:
Personal Information
We request personal information when you register as a member of this site. You
make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal
information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however,
you may not be able to use the activity/resource in question.
Cookies
When you register as a member of Aquaticcommunity.com, our Web server will send
a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to
your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A
cookie can't read data off your hard disk nor read cookie files created by other
Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you
when you are logged into the Aquaticcommunity.com network.
IP Adresses
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of
numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a
visitor requests a page from any Web site within the Aquaticcommunity.com
network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and
IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you
other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this
information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate miss use of
the Aquaticcommunity.com, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement.
Information usage:
Any and all information you willingly disclose to
Aquaticcommunity.com network is held strictly confidential. We will not sell
any personally identifying information obtained through this Web site to any
other organization, and we will never willfully disclose any personal
identification information about our audience to any third party.
Aquaticcommunity
mainpage
